shopperboard.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy - ShopperBoard

## Information Collection and Use

Tip We collect and use your information below to provide our Services and to measure and improve them over time.

**Information Collected Upon Registration:** When you create or reconfigure a ShopperBoard account, you provide some personal information, such as your name, username, password, and email address. Some of this information, for example, your name and username, is listed publicly on our Services, including on your profile page.

**Additional Information:** You may provide us with profile information to make public, such as a short biography, your location, your website, or a picture. You have an official email that is linked to your ShopperBoard account. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services or to market to you. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. If you connect your ShopperBoard account with Facebook in order to find or invite friends and eventually share products from ShopperBoard with them, Facebook may send us your registration or profile information and other information that you authorize.

**Saved Products, Following, Boards and other Public Information:** Our Services are primarily designed to help you save products from any online store and share it with the ShopperBoard community. Most of the information you provide us is information you are asking us to make public. This includes not only the products you add from online stores, but also the boards you create, the people you follow, and many other bits of information that result from your use of the Services. Our default is almost always to make the information you provide public for as long as you do not delete it from ShopperBoard, but we generally do not make it compulsory for you to include information you do not want to on your profile, for example.Your public information is broadly and instantly disseminated. For instance, users may click on your profile page and find out what products you save, who you are following, etc. When you save products and comment on product pages, you should think carefully about what you are making public.

**Links:** ShopperBoard may keep track of how you interact with links across our Services, including our email notifications, third-party services, and client applications, by redirecting clicks or through other means. We do this to help improve our Services, to provide more relevant advertising, and to be able to share aggregate click statistics such as how many times a particular link was clicked on.

**Cookies:** Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services, but we do not require cookies for many parts of our Services such as looking at public user profiles or boards. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. ShopperBoard may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to customize and improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. However, some Services may not function properly if you disable cookies.

**Log Data:** Our servers automatically record information (" **Log Data** ") created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, location, your mobile carrier, device and application IDs, search terms, and cookie information. We receive Log Data when you interact with our Services, for example, when you visit our websites, sign into our Services or interact with our email notifications. ShopperBoard uses Log Data to provide our Services and to measure, customize, and improve them. If not already done earlier, we will either delete Log Data or remove any common account identifiers, such as your username, full IP address, or email address, after 18 months.

**Third-Party Service Providers:** ShopperBoard uses a variety of third-party services to help provide our Services, such as hosting our various blogs and wikis, and to help us understand the use of our Services, such as Google Analytics. These third-party service providers may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP address.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

TipWe do not disclose your private personal information except in the limited circumstances described here.

**Your Consent:** We may share or disclose your information at your direction, such as when you authorize a third-party web client or application to access your ShopperBoard account.

**Service Providers:** We engage service providers to perform functions and provide services to us in Singapore and abroad. We may share your private personal information with such service providers subject to confidentiality obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy, and on the condition that the third parties use your private personal data only on our behalf and pursuant to our instructions.

**Law and Harm:** Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Policy, we may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect ShopperBoard's rights or property. However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to limit any legal defenses or objections that you may have to a third party’s, including a government’s, request to disclose your information.

**Business Transfers:** In the event that ShopperBoard is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this Privacy Policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity.

**Non-Private or Non-Personal Information:** We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as your public user profile information, public product saves, the people you follow or that follow you.
